https://floridaorchestra.org/privacy-policy/

About TFOPrivacy PolicyProtecting your private information is our priority. This Statement of Privacy applies to https://floridaorchestra.org, https://the.floridaorchestra.org, and The Florida Orchestra, and governs data collection and usage. For the purposes of this Privacy Policy, unless otherwise noted, all references to The Florida Orchestra include https://floridaorchestra.org and https://the.floridaorchestra.org. The Florida Orchestra website is an Events and Information site. By using The Florida Orchestra website, you consent to the data practices described in this statement.Collection of Your Personal InformationIn order to better provide you with products and services offered on our Site, The Florida Orchestra may collect personally identifiable information, such as your:•  First and Last Name •  Mailing Address •  E-mail Address •  Phone NumberIf you purchase The Florida Orchestra’s products and services, we collect billing and credit card information. This information is used to complete the purchase transaction.The Florida Orchestra may also collect anonymous demographic information, which is not unique to you, such as your:•  Age •  Gender •  Household IncomePlease keep in mind that if you directly disclose personally identifiable information or personally sensitive data through The Florida Orchestra’s public message boards, this information may be collected and used by others.We do not collect any personal information about you unless you voluntarily provide it to us. However, you may be required to provide certain personal information to us when you elect to use certain products or services available on the Site. These may include: (a) registering for an account on our Site; (b) entering a sweepstakes or contest sponsored by us or one of our partners; (c) signing up for special offers from selected third parties; (d) sending us an email message; (e) submitting your credit card or other payment information when ordering and purchasing products and services on our Site. To wit, we will use your information for, but not limited to, communicating with you in relation to services and/or products you have requested from us. We also may gather additional personal or non-personal information in the future.Use of Your Personal Information The Florida Orchestra collects and uses your personal information to operate its website(s) and deliver the services you have requested.The Florida Orchestra may also use your personally identifiable information to inform you of other products or services available from The Florida Orchestra and its affiliates.Sharing Information with Third PartiesThe Florida Orchestra does not sell, rent or lease its customer lists to third parties.The Florida Orchestra may, from time to time, contact you on behalf of external business partners about a particular offering that may be of interest to you. In those cases, your unique personally identifiable information (e-mail, name, address, telephone number) is not transferred to the third party. The Florida Orchestra may share data with trusted partners to help perform statistical analysis, send you email or postal mail, provide customer support, or arrange for deliveries. All such third parties are prohibited from using your personal information except to provide these services to The Florida Orchestra, and they are required to maintain the confidentiality of your information.The Florida Orchestra may disclose your personal information, without notice, if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to: (a) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on The Florida Orchestra or the site; (b) protect and defend the rights or property of The Florida Orchestra; and/or (c) act under exigent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of The Florida Orchestra, or the public.Tracking User BehaviorThe Florida Orchestra may keep track of the websites and pages our users visit within The Florida Orchestra, in order to determine what Florida Orchestra services are the most popular. This data is used to deliver customized content and advertising within The Florida Orchestra to customers whose behavior indicates that they are interested in a particular subject area.Automatically Collected InformationInformation about your computer hardware and software may be automatically collected by The Florida Orchestra. This information can include: your IP address, browser type, domain names, access times and referring website addresses. This information is used for the operation of the service, to maintain quality of the service, and to provide general statistics regarding use of The Florida Orchestra website.Use of CookiesThe Florida Orchestra website may use “cookies” to help you personalize your online experience. A cookie is a text file that is placed on your hard disk by a web page server. Cookies cannot be used to run programs or deliver viruses to your computer. Cookies are uniquely assigned to you and can only be read by a web server in the domain that issued the cookie to you.One of the primary purposes of cookies is to provide a convenience feature to save you time. The purpose of a cookie is to tell the Web server that you have returned to a specific page. For example, if you personalize The Florida Orchestra pages or register with The Florida Orchestra site or services, a cookie helps The Florida Orchestra to recall your specific information on subsequent visits. This simplifies the process of recording your personal information, such as billing addresses, shipping addresses, and so on. When you return to the same Florida Orchestra website, the information you previously provided can be retrieved, so you can easily use The Florida Orchestra features that you customized.You have the ability to accept or decline cookies. Most Web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. If you choose to decline cookies, you may not be able to fully experience the interactive features of The Florida Orchestra services or websites you visit.Security of Your Personal InformationThe Florida Orchestra secures your personal information from unauthorized access, use, or disclosure. The Florida Orchestra uses the following methods for this purpose:•  SSL ProtocolWhen personal information (such as a credit card number) is transmitted to other websites, it is protected through the use of encryption, such as the Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) protocol.We strive to take appropriate security measures to protect against unauthorized access to or alteration of your personal information. Unfortunately, no data transmission over the Internet or any wireless network can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, while we strive to protect your personal information, you acknowledge that: (a) there are security and privacy limitations inherent to the Internet which are beyond our control; and (b) security, integrity, and privacy of any and all information and data exchanged between you and us through this Site cannot be guaranteed.Right to DeletionSubject to certain exceptions set out below, on receipt of a verifiable request from you, we will:•  Delete your personal information from our records; and •  Direct any service providers to delete your personal information from their records.Please note that we may not be able to comply with requests to delete your personal information if it is necessary to:•  Complete the transaction for which the personal information was collected, fulfill the terms of a written warranty or product recall conducted in accordance with federal law, provide a good or service requested by you, or reasonably anticipated within the context of our ongoing business relationship with you, or otherwise perform a contract between you and us;•  Detect security incidents, protect against malicious, deceptive, fraudulent, or illegal activity; or prosecute those responsible for that activity;•  Debug to identify and repair errors that impair existing intended functionality;•  Exercise free speech, ensure the right of another consumer to exercise his or her right of free speech, or exercise another right provided for by law;•  Comply with the California Electronic Communications Privacy Act;•  Engage in public or peer-reviewed scientific, historical, or statistical research in the public interest that adheres to all other applicable ethics and privacy laws, when our deletion of the information is likely to render impossible or seriously impair the achievement of such research, provided we have obtained your informed consent;•  Enable solely internal uses that are reasonably aligned with your expectations based on your relationship with us;•  Comply with an existing legal obligation; or•  Otherwise use your personal information, internally, in a lawful manner that is compatible with the context in which you provided the information.Children Under ThirteenThe Florida Orchestra does not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under the age of thirteen. If you are under the age of thirteen, you must ask your parent or guardian for permission to use this website.E-mail CommunicationsFrom time to time, The Florida Orchestra may contact you via email for the purpose of providing announcements, promotional offers, alerts, confirmations, surveys, and/or other general communication. In order to improve our Services, we may receive a notification when you open an email from The Florida Orchestra or click on a link therein.If you would like to stop receiving marketing or promotional communications via email from The Florida Orchestra, you may opt out of such communications via email.External Data Storage SitesWe may store your data on servers provided by third party hosting vendors with whom we have contracted.Changes to this StatementThe Florida Orchestra reserves the right to change this Privacy Policy from time to time. We will notify you about significant changes in the way we treat personal information by sending a notice to the primary email address specified in your account, by placing a prominent notice on our site, and/or by updating any privacy information on this page. Your continued use of the Site and/or Services available through this Site after such modifications will constitute your: (a) acknowledgment of the modified Privacy Policy; and (b) agreement to abide and be bound by that Policy.Contact InformationThe Florida Orchestra welcomes your questions or comments regarding this Statement of Privacy. If you believe that The Florida Orchestra has not adhered to this Statement, please contact The Florida Orchestra at:The Florida Orchestra 244 2nd Avenue North #420 St. Petersburg, Florida 33701 Email Address: admin@floridaorchestra.org Telephone number: 727-892-3331Effective as of January 01, 2020 Mission & HistoryConductorsMusiciansStaff & BoardEmployment & AuditionsCommunity ReportContact Us
The Florida Orchestra
THE FLORIDA ORCHESTRA Certificate: 85-8012557655C-5 501(C)(3) Organization 244 2nd Avenue North · Suite 420 · St. Petersburg, FL 33701 Tel: 727.892.3331 · Fax: 727.892.3338 Privacy Policy
Scroll to top
